J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Aug. 14; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Sept. 1; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to Peter and Susan I. Lesley, 1866 Sept. 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Sept. 12; Trumbull, David (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Sept. 14; Wright, Chauncey (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Oct. 3; Winsor, Henry (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Nov. 1; Winsor, Henry (Box 9)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1866 Nov. 9; Hale, Charles (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Nov. 18; Bost, Leon and Sophie (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Nov. 18; Winsor, Henry (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Nov. 22; Reeves, Samuel J. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Nov. 27; Winsor, Henry (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Dec. 4; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Dec. 11; Desor, Edouard (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Dec. 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 Dec. 22; Garnier, C. F. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866; Bost, Samuel (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Jan. 3; Howe, Estes (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 Jan. 6; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Jan. 7; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Jan. 20; Wood, George Bacon (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 Jan. 25; Wright, Chauncey (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Jan. 25; James, Thomas P. (Box 10)
  - to H. R. Lyman, 1867 Jan. 30; Stewart, J. (Box 10)
  - to "Dear Sister, 1867 Feb. 7; Lyman, E. H. R. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Feb. 16; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Feb. 17; Kendall, E. O.. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 March 13; Dyke, P. B. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susie Lesley, 1867 March 13; Ware, William R. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1867 March 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - Thomas P. James to J. Peter Lesley APS business, 1867 March 23 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 April 11; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Bessie D. Baird to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 April 14 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867? April 15; Dean, John (Box 10)
  - A. Bost, pere to Mrs. S. E. Lesley, 1867 April 18 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 April 20; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 April 21; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 April 30; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Benjamin Franklin Peale to J. P. Lesley, 1867 May 4 (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 May 9; Dean, Lizzie P. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 May 12; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - M. V. Henderson to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 May 12 (Box 10)
  - Henry C. Baird to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 May 14 (Box 10)
  - Theodore Bergner to J. P. Lesley, 1867 May 17 (Box 10)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1867? May 20; Dean, John (Box 10)
  - Thomas P. James to J. P. Lesley, 1867 May 20 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 May 25; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 May 29; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 May 30; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 June 3; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 June 7; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 June 8; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 June 8; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 June 13; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 June 20; Bost, Theodore (Box 10)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. Lesley, 1867 June 24; Dyke, P. B. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 June 25; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 June 26; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 June 27; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 June 27; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 June 28; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 June 28; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 June 29; Dean, Lizzie P. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 June 29; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - Brown Shipley Co. to J. P. Lesley, 1867 July 3 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 July 4; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867? July 7; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - Carriage ticket for T. Sterry Hunt, In Europe..., 1867 July 9 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 July 23; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 July 26; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 July 27; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 July 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 July 28; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Aug. 1; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 Aug. 2; Shaler, S. P. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Aug. 3; Shaler, N. S. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Aug. 6; Dean, John (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 Aug. 8; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Aug. 13; Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Aug. 13; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Aug. 19; Granville, A. R. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867? Aug. 20; Dean, John (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1867 Aug. 21; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 Aug. 26; Hale, Charles (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Aug. 26; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 10)
  - to M. T. Bost, 1867 Sept. 13; Bush, S. W. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Sept. 14; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Sept. 18; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Sept. 30; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Sept. 30; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 10)
  - to J. P.Lesley, Oct. 1; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Oct. 7; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Oct. 11; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Henry C. Baird to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Oct. 20 (Box 10)
  - Charles Sumner to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Oct. 20 (Box 10)
  - A. B. Tawney to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Oct. 26 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Nov. 2; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Nov. 10; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - John Childs and Son to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Nov. 12 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Nov. 15; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, Nov. 15; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - John Childs and Son to N. Trübner, Nov. 15 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Nov. 17; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 Nov. 20; Thayer, J. B. (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1867 Dec. 1; Thayer, J. B. (Box 10)
  - and Co. to J. P. Lesley, 1867 Dec. 5; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Mary G. Bost to J. Peter Lesley, 1867 Dec. 7 (Box 10)
  - Selina Harris to Peter Lesley, ca. 1867 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Jan. 7, 8; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - John Childs and Son to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Jan. 23 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Feb. 8; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - and Co. to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Feb. 25; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 March 3; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Benjamin Franklin Peale to J.P. Lesley, 1868 March 12 (Box 10)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1868 March 13; Hale, Charles (Box 10)
  - Thomas P. James to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 March 13 (Box 10)
  - R. Sturguss to J. P. Lesley, enclosing letter of credit of Baring Bros. Co., London., 1868 March 20 (Box 10)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1868 March 22; Hale, Charles (Box 10)
  - Deouard Desor to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 March 25 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 March 25; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 March 26; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - M. D. Conway to Mr. Lesley, 1868 April 3 (Box 10)
  - Sir Charles Lyell, bart., to J. P. Lesley, 1868 April 3 (Box 10)
  - Marie Prélet to Madame Lesley, 1868 April 8 (Box 10)
  - M. D. Conway to Mrs. Lesley, 1868 April 10 (Box 10)
  - Marie Prélet to Madame Lesley, 1868 April 10 (Box 10)
  - Andrew Ramsay to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 April 10 (Box 10)
  - M. D. Conway to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 April 13 (Box 10)
  - J. Bute Lukes to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 April 13 (Box 10)
  - W. Marcet to J. P. Lesley, 1868 April 14 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 April 15-21; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - Russell Sturgis to Mrs. Lesley, 1868 April 24 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 May 3; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 May 6; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - W. Marcet to J. P. Lesley, 1868 May 6 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 May 15; Bost, A. (Box 10)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1868 May 15; Hale, Charles (Box 10)
  - L. Lesquereux to Peter Lesley, 1868 May 24 (Box 10)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. Lesley, 1868 June 4; Dyke, P. B. (Box 10)
  - Anna Ticknor to Mrs. Lesley, 1868 June 4 (Box 10)
  - Salima Harris to Mr. Lesley, 1868 June 5 (Box 10)
  - to Mr. J. P. Lesley, 1868 June 5; Thayer, J. B. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 June 13; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 June 17; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 June 19; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1868 June 21; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - J. M. Forbes to Mr. Lesley, 1868 June 28 (Box 10)
  - Note to James B. Thayer for $500.00..., 1868 July 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 10)
  - to J. P.Lesley, 1868 July 3; Thayer, J. B. (Box 10)
  - to "J. Peter Lesley", 1868 July 3; Winsor, Henry (Box 10)
  - R. Van Lennep to Mr. Lesley, 1868 July 4 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 July 4; Truübner, N. (Box 10)
  - H. A. Henderson to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 5 (Box 10)
  - N. H. Morison to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 8 (Box 10)
  - Anne C. L. Botta to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 July 9 (Box 10)
  - to N. H. Morison, 1868 July 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 10)
  - George Ripley to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 11 (Box 10)
  - Anne C. L. Botta to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 July 14 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 18; Thayer, J. B. (Box 10)
  - to Mr. and Mrs. Lesley, 1868 July 20; Dyke, P. B. (Box 10)
  - J. B. Lippincott to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 20 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 July 21; Reeves, Samuel J. (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 July 24; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - to N. Trübner, 1868 July 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 10)
  - James T. Hodge to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 July 26 (Box 10)
  - J. T. Hodge to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Aug. 5 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Aug. 6; Hall, James (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Aug. 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1868 Aug. 12; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - N. H. Morison to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Aug. 13 (Box 10)
  - Samuel Dinsmoor to E. P. Flower, 1868? Aug. 13 (Box 10)
  - E. F. Flower to Mr. Lesley, 1868 Aug. 14 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Aug. 16; Bost, Theodore (Box 10)
  - Nathan Hale to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Aug. 16 (Box 10)
  - A. D. White to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Aug. 26 (Box 10)
  - E de Goldberg to Mr. Peter Lesley, 1868 Sept. 1 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Sept. 13; Hall, James (Box 10)
  - J. Lesley to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Sept. 14 (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Oct. 3; Desor, Edouard (Box 10)
  - J. D. Lesley to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Oct. 8 (Box 10)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1868 Nov. 6; Moore, Ira. (Box 10)
  - to Mr. Lesley, 1868? Dec. 5; Hale, Charles (Box 10)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1868 Dec. 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 10)
  - Sidney S. Lyon to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Jan. 18 (Box 11)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1869 Feb. 18; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 11)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1869 Feb. 25; Hale, Susan (Box 11)
  - Report on York County iron ores, to T. A. Scott, 1869 March 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to T. A. Scott on the Towanda Stell process., 1869 March 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to Sir Charles Lyell, bart., 1869 April 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Memorandum on editing W. S. R. R. and Mining Register, 1869 April 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Memorandum of agreement to edit U. S. R. R. and Mining Register..., 1869 April 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Memorandum... U. S. R. R. and Mining Register..., 1869 April 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Sir Charles Lyell, bart. to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 May 10 (Box 11)
  - George Rolliston to J. P. Lesley, 1869 May 29 (Box 11)
  - R. P. Rothwell to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 June 2 (Box 11)
  - R. P. Rothwell to J. P. Lesley, 1869 June 9 (Box 11)
  - to Thomas A. Scott, 1869 June 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Alex Winchell to J. P. Lesley, 1869 June 26 (Box 11)
  - to A. Winchell, 1869 July 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1869 July 24; Winchell, Alexander (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 June 28; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1869 July 2; Hale, Susan (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Sept. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1869 Sept. 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - Sir Charles Lyell, bart. to J. P. Lesley, 1869 Oct. 11 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Oct. 19; Desor, Edouard (Box 11)
  - Ouis Agassiz to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Nov. 1 (Box 11)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1869 Nov. 14; Revere, Josie (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1869 Nov. 20; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Nov. 22; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1869 Nov. 30; Truübner, N. (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1869 Dec. 6; Brooks, T. B. (Box 11)
  - A. H. W orthen to J. P. Lesley, 1869 Dec. 14 (Box 11)
  - John L. LeConte to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Dec. 15 (Box 11)
  - Benjamin Peirce to J. Peter Lesley, 1869 Dec.? 18 (Box 11)
  - Bills from J. B. Lippincott, American Continental Literary Agency, Trübner and Co. to J. Peter Lesley for publications and materials including shipment to Sir Charles Lyell, the APS. etc., 1869-1870 (Box 11)
  - C. H. Hitchock to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Jan. 18 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Jan. 28; Whitney, J. D. (Box 11)
  - Robert Briggs to Mr. Peter Lesley, 1870 Feb. 13 (Box 11)
  - Robert Briggs, Trübner and Co. to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Feb. 16 (Box 11)
  - Montgomery C. Meigs to J. P. Lesley, 1870 March 26 (Box 11)
  - Eligabeth L. Smith to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1870 March 26 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 April 20; Quincy, Edmund (Box 11)
  - Maria Revere to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1870 April 26 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 April 29; Quincy, Edmund (Box 11)
  - Report to the Pennsylvania Rail Road Company on Morrison's Cove ore Banks., 1870 May 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1870 June 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 June 14; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1870 June 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - Report on iron ore in Morrison's Cove, for the Pennsylvania Railroad Company., 1870 June 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870? June 23; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 11)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1870 July 11; Clarke, James Freeman, 1810-1888 (Box 11)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1870 July 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - John G. Trautwine to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Aug. 6 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Aug. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - J. Edgar Thomson to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Aug. 25 (Box 11)
  - E. T. Cox to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Sept. 23 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Nov. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - to E. T. Cox, 1870 Nov. 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Nov. 15; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Nov. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Nov. 24; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Nov. 29; Henry, Joseph (Box 11)
  - Report to T. A. Scott, summary of observations in South West Virginia..., 1870 Nov.; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - C. H. Hitchcock to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Dec. 3 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Dec. 5; Newberry, J. S., (John Strong), 1822-1892 (Box 11)
  - to John Edgar Thomson on the coal property of the Danville, Hazelton and Wilkesbarre Railroad Co., 1870 Dec. 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to F. H. Hedge, 1870 Dec. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1870 Dec. 23; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 11)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1870 Dec.; Hall, James (Box 11)
  - Detailed report on the mountain counties of S. W. Virginia... iron ores, coal gypsum, and salt., 1870 Dec.; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to John W. Guery, 1870?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Note on the Scallop Shell of the Myteries read before the APS, 1870; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Novel: incomplete: "Frank", ca. 1870; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - Report to Messrs Findlay and Hay, Salisbury, Pa., on coal lands near Salisbury., 1870; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 11)
  - to T. A. Scott on the Harrisville coal beds in Butler County, Penna., 1871 Jan. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Jan. 14; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Jan. 18; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Jan. 21; Hall, James (Box 12)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Jan. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to E. M. Davis reporting on the geology of coal lands in Kentucky., 1871 Jan. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - W. Hardinger to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Feb. 2 (Box 12)
  - Thomas S. Ridgway to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Feb. 7 (Box 12)
  - to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Feb. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Feb. 12; Henderson, A. A. (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Feb. 13; Hayden, F. V., (Ferdinand Vandeveer), 1829-1887 (Box 12)
  - Report to A. J. Cassett on Bell's coal bank run track., 1871 Feb. 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Feb. 23; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Feb. 26; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 12)
  - J. W. Harden. Report to J. P. Lesley on the coal and ironstone beds... in Blair Co., Pa...., 1871 March 3 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 March 6; Hall, James (Box 12)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1871 March 8; Worthen, A. H. (Box 12)
  - to C. W. Stone, 1871 March 12; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 March 13; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1871 March 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 March 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to Susan I. Lesley, 1871 March 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 March 29; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 12)
  - Report to Thomas Graham on the Tuscarora Iron Ore belt in North Carolina., 1871 March; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 April 2; Hall, James (Box 12)
  - Hannah C. Stears to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 April 18 (Box 12)
  - to Thomas Graham reporting on surveys in Somerset County, Penna., 1871 April 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - Report on the property of William J. Buer, Somerset County, Penna., 1871 April 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to Thomas A. Scott reporting on the properties of the Tennessee Iron and Coal Co. in East Tennessee and Kentucky, 1871 April 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to Mrs. E. Er. Clement, 1871 April 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 April 30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 May 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 May 8; Henry, Joseph (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 May 10; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 May 17; Henry, Joseph (Box 12)
  - Henry S. Poole to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 May 18 (Box 12)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1871 May 24; Hale, Edward Everett, 1822-1909 (Box 12)
  - R. P. Rothwell to J. P. Lesley, 1871 May 24 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 May 25; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 12)
  - W. S. Shaler to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 May 29 (Box 12)
  - to J. Winters. Report to Messrs Scott, Delano, Cameron, and others on the Tennessee Iron and Coal Co's. property..., 1871 May; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - Henry S. Poole to J. P. Lesley, 1871 June 2 (Box 12)
  - to Howard Spencer and others report on the Henry Rope and John Kunkle tracts..., 1871 June 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 June 9; Quincy, Edmund (Box 12)
  - Report on the Henry Rope and John Kunkle tracts..., 1871 June; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - Maria R. Towne to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 July 10 (Box 12)
  - Andrew Ramsay to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 July 17 (Box 12)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 July 18; Thayer, J. B. (Box 12)
  - to Robert Hare Powel, reporting on ore outcrops on Tussey Mountain..., 1871 July 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - to J. H. McBride on certaon tracts of land in Somerset and Bedford Counties, Penna., 1871 July 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - Henry S. Polle to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Aug. 2 (Box 12)
  - Henry Morton to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Aug. 10 (Box 12)
  - E. T. Cox to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Aug. 14 (Box 12)
  - Charles William Eliot to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Aug. 16 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Aug. 18; Fulton, John (Box 12)
  - Mrs. Caroline S. Guild to Peter Lesley, 1871 Aug. 19 (Box 12)
  - to Mr. Agassiz, 1871 Aug. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 12)
  - Henry S. Poole to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Aug. 26 (Box 12)
  - Henry W. Bellows to Mrs. White, 1871 Sept. 5 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Sept. 6; Hunt, T. Sterry (Box 12)
  - F. A. Genth to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 7 (Box 12)
  - Henry W. Bellos to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Sept. 11 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 17; Hall, James (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Sept. 19; Brooks, T. B. (Box 12)
  - W. P. Blake to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Sept. 24 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 25; Desor, Edouard (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 27; Hall, James (Box 12)
  - "A Friend" to Mrs. Susna I. Lesley, 1871 Sept. 28 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Sept. 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - John J. Stevenson to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Sept. 30 (Box 12)
  - Annie Fields to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 2 (Box 12)
  - Mrs. James Tolman and Family to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Oct. 3 (Box 12)
  - P. T. Jackson to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 5 (Box 12)
  - Benjamin Peirce to J. P. Lesley, 1871 Oct. 8 (Box 12)
  - Julia S. Goodfellow to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 9 (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Oct. 10; Bost, John (Box 12)
  - Charlotte M. Haven to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871? Oct. 11 (Box 12)
  - William L. Learned to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Oct. 16 (Box 12)
  - Sarah B. Shaw to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 16 (Box 12)
  - George A. Goddard to Mrs. Susan I. Lyman Lesley, 1871 Oct. 18 (Box 12)
  - Ella F. Mosley to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Oct. 21 (Box 12)
  - William A. Hale to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 22 (Box 12)
  - to Mary Lesley, 1871 Oct. 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 12)
  - Russell N. Bellows to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1871 Oct. 28 (Box 12)
  - Letter to Mrs. Susan I. Lesley, 1871 Oct. 29 (Box 12)
  - John Tyndall to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Oct. 31 (Box 12)
  - to Joseph Lesley, 1871 Nov. 7; Henderson, A. A. (Box 12)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1871 Nov. 8; Henderson, A. A. (Box 12)